So DeepSeek,
which is the cheapest
AI in the world,
just started charging
rush hour prices.
And these increases run
from 50% all the way
to 1100%.
And the reason
is because they want
people to use
it at night instead.
So some examples
that are similar
to this are like train
fare pricing and Uber
surge pricing.
The interesting thing
though is softwares
never work like this.
Like this is kind
of how electricity
and energy bills run.
Like Netflix does not
charge you extra
for watching a movie
on Friday night.
I mean, I guess
it makes sense.
When you're using
AI models, you are
running on a real
physical chip,
like using electricity
in a real building.
I wonder how it will pan
out though because
DeepSeek is known
for being the cheapest
AI.
And OpenAI just cut one
of its prices by
like 80%.